<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jinlai Xu&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>http://jinlaixu.net/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jinlai Xu&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Jinlai Xu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jinlaixu.net/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Federated Cloud</title>
      <link>http://jinlaixu.net/project/contracts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jinlaixu.net/project/contracts/</guid>
      <description>Overview We develop a new contracts-based resource sharing model for federated geo-distributed clouds that allows cloud service providers to establish contractual relationships with individual datacenters for defined time intervals. Based on the established contracts, individual cloud service providers employ a cost-aware job scheduling and provisioning algorithm that enables tasks to complete and meet their response time requirements.
What is the challenge?  How to decide Resource Sharing Contracts guaranteeing both Fairness and Efficiency?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PADS</title>
      <link>http://jinlaixu.net/project/pads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jinlaixu.net/project/pads/</guid>
      <description>Overview PADS is a strategy-proof differentially private auction mechanism designed to allow cloud providers to trade resources with consumers in such a way that individual bidding information of the consumers do not get exposed through the auction mechanism. PADS provides differential privacy and approximate truthfulness guarantees while maintaining good performance in terms of revenue earned and allocation efficiency.
What is the challenge?  Protect Each User&amp;rsquo;s Bidding Information through the Auctioning Mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zenith</title>
      <link>http://jinlaixu.net/project/zenith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jinlaixu.net/project/zenith/</guid>
      <description>Overview In the Internet of Things(IoT) era, the demands for low-latency computing for time-sensitive applications (e.g., location-based augmented reality games, real-time smart grid management, real-time navigation using wearables) has been growing rapidly. Edge Computing provides an additional layer of infrastructure to fill latency gaps between IoT devices and the backend computing infrastructure.
Zenith decouples resource allocation and service provisioning and management at the edge and provides a novel model to allocate resources at the edge to maximize utility.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>